(Leonard:)Stop it, you're gonna make me cry.
I (ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS) I
(Leonard:)All right, you seem pretty confident.
(Penny:)Oh, I am.
(Penny:)Maybe if you follow this trail,
(Penny:)you'll see why.
(Leonard:)-Oh... Rose petals.
-Yes.
(Penny:)The most beautiful and shockingly
expensive of all the flowers.
(Leonard:)You made the bed? You really
are pulling out all the stops.
(Penny:)Okay, I gave this a lot of thought,
(Penny:)and I finally found something
to show you how much I love you.
(Leonard:)Oh, wow.
(Penny:)It's a first edition
of Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
(Penny:)I remember it was your
favourite book growing up.
(Leonard:)This is great.
(Penny:)Thank you... so much.
(Amy:)What?
(Leonard:)Nothing. I love it.
No, somethings going on.
What's wrong with it?